The formidable Giri Double Six once
conquered the North Blue by force.
It's hard to believe
that tomorrow your regime
of terror abruptly ends
with a hail of bullets.
The wedding will be...
Soaked red with your blood. Bang.
By the way, I would
appreciate one last favor.
Can you make it a point not to create
too big of a mess when you die tomorrow?
Just be mindful of the splatter.
If that wedding cake gets
one drop of blood on it,
Mama will be livid and no one wants that.
She'd tear the place down out of fury.
See this?
It's a 36-caliber Walker
Percussion Pistol.
The bullets it fires are
called Candy Jackets.
They are designed to be able to penetrate
through the toughest armor and shields.
As you can see, it works rather well.
Even your tempered body
can be pierced by these.
Can you imagine Sanji's face
when he sees the girl he trusted?
Pointing a gun right between his eyes.
Delicious!
It's gonna be good!
That sad sack actually believes
that you have real feelings for him?
He doesn't suspect a thing.
The poor fool.
I wonder what kind of face he'll make?
Oh, I know!
Maybe something like this?
They really nailed it!
I can see it now!
Or how about this one? Ready?
P-p-pudding, my sweet!
Come on, why aren't you looking?
This is hilarious.
Don't like us making fun of your brother?
Live a little.
Laughing can take the edge off.
Got nothing to lose.
You want to know how he proposed?
It was hilarious.
and pretty embarrassing, honestly,
he pulled his face back off,
and his whole head was fat and bloated.
and ugly—it was too easy in
that moment of vulnerability;
all I had to do was fake some tears,
and he was putty if you decide to
marry me—I won't let it be hell!
be hell
Oh, well, men are stupid creatures.
Then that fool pulled me close,
just like in a Clutch romance novel.
And uttered some trash
in this soft whisper.
You're my salvation, pudding!
So if you'll have me, let's get married.
Honestly, could you imagine
a more pitiful proposal?
Oh, what a riot.
What kind of idiot would win a
colossal failure like him? Seriously?
The nerve of you, trying to pass him off?
At least bring me a
proper Prince to marry.
What?
Granting me courage, I
hope that we'll never stop.
No matter where you
are, nothing is too far.
With our everlasting bones,
we'll reach it, we are home.
I'm so truly grateful I ran into
you on that day so long ago.
We laughed every moment with tears in
our eyes till we knew we weren't alone.
The blowing wind came in
and joined us on our way.
And with it I know we'll rise.
We'll be flying up high.
Why, tell me why are you giving up?
Why, tell me why you want to fight alone?
Hey, what kind of future
do you think you have?
Your dream is already in your hands.
This love in my heart,
it will burn off forever.
Granting me courage, I
hope it will never stop.
And no matter where you
are, nothing needs truth on.
With our everlasting plans,
we'll reach it, we are home.
From the horizon, out on
the edge of the world.
If there was a place that
I'd want to take you to.
Let's head for it then, but ask
for the way we already know.
We promised it long ago.
You scream by your voice that
can't break through the silence.
Feeling defeated, it
crushes your helpless heart.
I've got your back, I
swear, I'll always be here.
Let's put our fate within
this light under the sun.
Can you close your eyes and
just listen to my voice.
Let's find the answer
together, I'm telling you.
In our path I trust that it will lead us.
To another sea untarded,
cause now we are home.
On the horizon, out on
the edge of the world.
There is a place that I wanna take you to.
Let's head forward then,
but ask for the way.
We already know.
We promised it long ago.
Are you still trying to stand?
I am.
Why hurt yourself?
You must really want another
thrashing, don't you?
You want that stone so badly, huh?
You're not trying to rescue Sanji,
leaving him and focusing on the
polyglyph instead. That's right.
There's one thing about
Sanji; he's kind to a fault,
so I thought right from the start
that he might not be returning to our
crew—that isn't to say I've figured out
exactly what trap you've set for him.
But knowing Sanji's considerate nature,
if he's made up his mind to
sacrifice himself for someone,
then he will not back down.
Our captain on the other
hand will follow his
heart fearlessly and see
this through to the end.
So I have faith in the both of
them to settle things on their own.
It's
all up to them then—you're useless,
just coming to play with my poneglyph
because you're bored, not at all.
If worse comes to worst and Sanji
decides to stay here of his own accord?
own accord
I do not want him to
be riddled with guilt.
Rather,
I want him to know that this journey allowed
us to accomplish something essential.
So I must succeed.
That Poneglyph's message is ours.
Ma!
I think that your idea of
worst-case scenario is rather tame.
Sanji staying behind,
that's the worst outcome.
Try again.
Has the thought even crossed your
mind that everyone might die?
Only a fool would include his own
death as part of a plan, young lady.
No, no, no!
Tickle, tickle, tickle!
Answer the question and I'll stop!
Otherwise, it's more of Carrot's
special tickle, tickle, tickle!
I can't! I can't!
I can't take it, you little brat!
Just spit it out!
She can do this all day! Don't try her!
Fine!
Fine, I'll tell!
You heard her, Carrot!
You can stop, all right?
I'll make you pay
So where is it then?
Which one's the castle's entrance?
Do you honestly think that I can remember
where every single mirror leads to?
That's not the answer we're looking for.
You just gotta ask the mirrors themselves!
Like talk to them?
Is that a joke?
I'm not lying.
Ask the stupid things yourself.
All the mirrors know
what they're reflecting.
Magic mirrors in the hall!
Which one leads us to
the castle wall? Not me!
Also me! I know that!
Me as well!
They actually answered us!
I can assist with that! I'll do it!
I'll take you there!
And I can transport you
into Lady Galant's closet!
I'm a hand mirror in a guest
room on the second floor.
I've got ladies room
for a floor over here.
Are any of you reflecting our buddies
Luffy, Nambi, Brooke, Pedro, or Sanji?
That's who we're looking for!
Who are they?
What do they look like?
I caught a glimpse of Sanji earlier.
Oh, that's right.
He wouldn't know what
everybody looks like.
Count on me, Cho-Bro.
I'm a pretty good artist.
I didn't realize that.
Uh-huh.
it must be embarrassing to have such
a dim-witted brother yeah he's so dumb
hey uh it looks like a little hostage is
gonna pass out soon if she croaks that'll
ruin our whole plan and that won't do we
still want her to attend
tomorrow's ceremony
me listen close dear sister-in-law i
can't have you bleeding
to death on us and i
certainly don't want to risk you ratting
on me for all my
unladylike behavior tonight
What is this?
Just relax.
It won't take long.
Oh, come on.
That wasn't so bad, right?
Everyone carries unpleasant memories.
and trauma we'd rather forget,
how wonderful would it be not
to remember all that nonsense.
this is the power of the memo memo fruit,
Germa double six's
technology; sure is something.
despite being shot in the leg, you dragged
yourself pretty far—not that it matters.
I'll
just paste this memory
from a soldier who was
hit by a stray bullet
here and a quick edit.
and
that should do it; your memories
from tonight have all been rewritten.
let's have a lovely
wedding tomorrow—shall we
call the soldiers have
them take her to the ward?
yes, ma 'am.
i'm begging
you to stop looping that's enough already!
enough already
Just knock it off!
We're destroying your arms!
You think I care?
I gotta warn Satya about putting
me in evil! She's a liar!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
No!
Don't do it, Lupi! Ow, ow, ow!
Almost there!
I think he's going a little too far.
All right, let's talk, girl.
What do you want?
Can't you see I'm busy?
Mama's instructions were for me to obtain
Lola's whereabouts by
whatever means necessary.
So out with it already.
I won't tell.
I'd never betray my friends. Very well.
Guess you'll want to be tortured.
Don't make it sound so casual.
Ready?
I'm going to shoot you with
this once every five seconds.
I will stop when you choose to talk.
Something like that could kill me.
Are you crazy?
Don't do that.
Then start talking.
Screw you, warthead!
You'll have to go through me!
It's okay, Nami.
I'll be done breaking
my arms in just a sec.
What?
Not that either!
Quit being a baby!
Hey, is anyone in here?
Whoa, whoa!
I thought you were forbidden
from entering the castle anymore.
This island is ascending into chaos.
Now it has reached you as well.
I hope you can forgive me for this.
Now 5,000 bricks!
Finished!
My apologies.
Why don't you rest up for a while?
Jinbei!
Oh, Luffy! Nami!
Great timing!
Why are you here?
I heard you were taken captive.
I'm relieved to see that you're well.
We have catching up to do.
Right now, you must escape.
Thank you!
She got here in bad shape, but
evidently it's already healing up.
Her skin is tough, and it
heals unnaturally fast.
Jerma's augmented humans are
a marvel, to say the least.
I believe she'll recover in time for
tomorrow's tea party after a good night's rest.
She should be in the clear,
but monitor her vitals overnight
also, please notify the vinsmokes.
Surely they'll be worried, sir?
Well, I'll be at the medical
center on the fourth floor.
After all, there's plenty of wounded
soldiers in the Shit tonight.
I doubt I'll be able to
find the time to sleep,
thank you for your service, take care.
Where am I?
Sanji!
I hurt my leg.
Do you recall how you got
hurt, or what happened?
I remember walking around the castle,
and then came across some soldiers
who were shouting about intruders.
I must have gotten involved somehow.
Reizhu, think harder.
That's not it.
Your memories were overwritten.
I'll fill you in.
But let me warn you,
the truth is damn ugly.
These books are susceptible to fire!
Wait, you're going to torch
the cage with us inside?
Just leave the enclosure before
you're engulfed in flames.
It's really quite simple.
Do it then! Go! That quick?
Wait, I'm not on board yet!
Oh, we're gonna get incinerated!
Burn faster!
Burn! Lupus! Coming!
We're free now!
Damn it.
Why do I feel like I've been
through something like this before?
You survived. Well done.
Because of you, I didn't
have to rip my hands off.
So thanks.
It just struck me.
Do you remember the first
time we met each other?
Coincidentally, it was also in a prison.
And look, that very same cage.
also held all these
prisoners within its pages.
The world of books is as
infinite as your own imagination.
Do take note that Big Mom's allies
and lackeys are quite formidable.
Thanks a bunch, Chimbe.
So, what are you doing here? Well,
it's a bit complicated,
but as Captain of the Sun Pirates, I have
an affiliation with Big Mom and her crew.
Do you really?
Then what about all this?
I suppose you'd call it a rebellion.
No turning back now.
You're laughing?
But what about your responsibilities?
Wasn't that an issue?
I have cast them aside.
The screams came from the prison library.
What's going on? Great.
They already know.
Not surprising.
They're quick.
We must find a place to conceal ourselves.
Hurry, they draw close. Good call.
Here, follow me.
So we can't move.
Too hungry.
At a time like this? Truly? Oh, right.
Luffy burns out.
He expends energy three
times faster than others.
Don't worry.
I didn't say I needed to eat. I'm fine.
Luffy, your stomach speaks.
Ignore it.
Hey, Sanji!
I won't eat anything unless you cook it!
Even if I get hungry,
even if spears or swords or stones rain
down on me, I'll keep waiting for you!
Anyway, Jinbei, thank you.
The, uh, truth is, I met with
Sanji, and he proposed to me.
The reason why we're not
getting married is because
that love-born fool played
right into my hands.
And during the wedding ceremony, I
planned to shoot him full of holes.
Things are pretty bad as is.
We were all tricked by
them, Sanji included.
I need to warn him!
Look after Nami, Jinbei!
Just a word of caution.
There are many guards outside!
Also, you're not fully
recovered. Be careful.
You went through a lot this morning.
I'll be fine. I promise.
Think I'm lying?
I don't.
I know you would never mislead me.
I was wary of Pudding, but didn't
imagine her to be this devious.
I had my suspicions.
She just seemed a little too perfect for
me, so I thought I should eavesdrop a bit.
I really screwed up.
I assumed if I accepted the marriage,
they would spare my crewmates.
It turns out that was never in the cards.
It was all a ploy.
Of course they were blowing smoke up
my ass.
I thought everything would work
out if I took one for the team.
What kind of a fantasy was
I living in?
I should have known better.
They fooled our father, too.
He's a wise man, But he was
undone by his arrogance.
He's dealing with an emperor; he
should have been more cautious.
And now it's far too late—this
still might play out for the best,
though I believe that
Germa should be destroyed.
I'd like to pretend I'm ignorant
and let Big Mom carry out her plan.
Don't be stupid!
stupid They'll kill
you tomorrow too, Race!
Aw, is my little brother concerned for me?
Leave the past where it
lies, where beyond that.
You don't owe me a single thing.
I only helped you once before.
Go find the Straw Hats and leave
this island, Sanji. Like how?
I can't do that!
What do you think would
happen to the Baratier?
Just run.
Figure that out after you've escaped.
Stay here and all of you will die.
Sanji, you have to live
for our mother's sake.
Why bring her up?
Because there's one memory I can't forget.
What do you mean?
What memory?
There was a fight between our parents.
I was just a child at the time,
so I didn't understand the catalyst of our
mother's resentment of
father until much later.
But it's obvious in retrospect.
While our mother was still
carrying the four of you,
she was quite adamant against turning you
quadruplets into cold-blooded
killing machines.
You're not serious!
Of course I am. Never!
How could you do that to them?
Enough.
The surgery is already arranged.
Don't do this!
These are my children as well!
I beg you! Please, Judge!
They need their humanity!
Being human won't cut it.
Not when monsters win wars.
Our end goal is to reclaim the North Blue
by force and restore
it to its former glory.
Accomplishing that vision
will take incredible strength,
which is the reason I give
this gift to my own progeny!
Stop take her away
They forced the surgery on her
But our mother took a toxin attempting
to foil our father's plan he was furious
no what did you just do it was a
powerful drug strong enough to affect
the manipulated bloodline elements
unfortunately it wasn't enough
it didn't take long before superhuman like
abnormalities began
appearing in our brother's
Bodies the operation was a great success
wonderful I'm delighted to report
that their genetic blueprints were not
altered in any which way by the toxin
you wanna play master sanji on
the other hand is trailing behind
we'll monitor the boy perhaps
his development is a bit delayed
You two must be hungry.
Just one second.
Here.
Is it good?
Whoa!
Master Sanji is feeding animals.
He was supposed to be
devoid of emotions! Saru!
You were growing, but
not as father wanted.
You had compassion.
Meanwhile,
our mother got weaker and weaker due to
the long-term effects caused by the poison.
She died because of me, then?
Nonsense. Don't think that way.
Mother? Reiju!
Hello, dear.
How's your father treating you?
The only thing that he wants
to do is make us train.
It's dumb.
He's only happy when Ichiji,
Niji and Yonji get stronger.
I see what's that?
Take a look.
Sanji cooked me a meal all by himself!
Wow really.
Guess what Sanji told me
today that boy. It's so sweet
He said, get better.
He's the best son ever.
What are you doing here?
Uh, Dad...
Flowers for the dead is a pointless rite.
You're proving your uselessness.
Stop your crying!
What?!
Coward!
Let's go.
You too, Reiju.
Sir.
Our father's beliefs were
completely contrary to our mother's.
That's why he could never
accept who you were.
He blamed you for
everything that happened.
He lashed out at you as punishment.
There!
Don't ever cook again!
I'm pulling back!
Attack me!
How is Sanji such a worthless failure?
Failure! Failure!
Now go!
And don't look back!
Even though Mother has passed,
she's still here.
Her kindness lives on in you.
Needless to say,
you are no failure.
Just remember, our Mother
selflessly gave her life.
to protect you and your humanity.
You are the future Mother wanted to see.
That's why you're kinder
and more tender than anyone.
Find Straw Hat!
Which way did he go?
He escaped the underground prison library
and passed through the first floor!
Hurry up!
Head to the second floor!
Sir!
Sochi!
What do you mean there's another problem?
Well, there are reports that Boss
Jinbei's in the castle. Seriously?
He's rebelling?
Yes, it seems so.
All right.
Send this message to
the troops. Yes, ma 'am.
Tomorrow's a big day.
Don't disappoint Mama.
Of course not.
Do you know what will happen if we fail?
I asked a simple question.
What'll happen?
I don't even want to think about it.
Now you understand.
Considering that lesser inconveniences
have sent Mama into one of her mood swings,
we can't risk sabotaging tomorrow's plan.
Of course not.
But there's an easy way to avoid that.
You think we should lie?
If you lie to Mama, then
you'll be put to death.
Please forgive me.
You see, we don't need
to tell her anything.
If there is no problem.
You get what I'm saying?
Yes, I do, ma 'am.
We're on the fourth floor.
Block off all paths leading here.
Then make sure everything on
the lower levels is in order.
Get a move on it and
take care of the problem.
Yes, ma 'am. Understood.
But wait.
If we're in a hurry, it might be
faster just to kill them. Do whatever.
You have my permission.
Ma 'am!
Spit it out!
Where's Saint?
Saint!
I know he's here!
Just kill me!
What is there to think about, you know?
In your heart, what you should do.
Just abandon Germa and flee to safety—it
represents nothing but destruction.
Clinging to the glories of the past, the
world would be better off without us.
All
big mom wants is our military technology.
I
highly doubt she's interested
in taking your mentor's life.
After
the wedding tomorrow, our father
and brothers will all be dead.
dead Remember?
So it's fine They can't
carry out the threat.
Glorified murderers.
That's what our family has always been.
You know I can't stand all
those pretentious jerks!
But why do you have to die, Reizhu?
I still have my emotions intact.
But father augmented me, so
I am unable to disobey him.
There's no way out, Sanji!
But I have blood on my hands.
I deserve death.
Oh, by the way, those bracelets on you?
I promise that they won't explode.
I swap them out for normal ones.
What other reason could
be keeping you here?
Honestly.
Would you pull it together?
Wake up!
You need to think about
what really matters.
Wish it was that simple.
Stop, straw hands!
Excuse me, why don't you join my crew?
I could use a cook like you on my ship.
Nodgy!
You're a good cook, and I need one,
obviously—we should be pirates together.
You
have wonderful friends, people like
that—only come once in a lifetime.
Move on!
move on